VALENTINA GOTTARDEL

Full-Stack Software Developer



- 049 3258 402
- ∨alengottardello37@gmail.com
- in linkedin.com/in/valentinagottardello
- github.com/valegottardello
- https://myportfolio-valentinagottardello.vercel.app

PROFILE

I am a Full-Stack Software Developer with four years of experience in the legal field, followed by three years working in the fitness industry as a Head Coach-Manager.

With a strong dedication to my professional growth, I am driven to make a significant impact in the field of software engineering. I am always fully prepared to face challenges head-on.

TWO YEARS

GitHub

React Native

Postman

Material UI

Xcode

ONE YEAR

nede Node.is

express Express

Firebase

MongoDB

GraphQL

TypeScript

SKILLS

THREE YEARS

HTML



JavaScript







PostgreSQL



Tailwind CSS



Bootstrap



EDUCATION

GENERAL ASSEMBLY

Computer Software Engineering Full Stack Web Development - Tech Stack JavaScript, Node.Js, React. Feb 2023 - May 2023

CODERHOUSE

Web Developer Introduction to Web Development - Tech Stack HTML, CSS, SASS, CEO. Oct 2022 - Dec 2022

NATIONAL UNIVERSITY OF CORDOBA Associates Degree, Law Mar 2012 - Dec 2017

EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING PROJECTS

TO-DO APP

- · A simple and efficient to-do app built. It allows users to add, edit, and remove tasks from the task board, with three simple filters.
- · React &TypeScript
- · Link repo Link demo-video

FIXUP

- · A work space full-stack application, tailored for small businesses.
- · React...Js . Express & PostgreSOL
- · Link repo Link demo-video Link real-demo

MOVIESPLUS

- · Full-stack movies search application with user registration and saved movies list functionality.
- · React, Tailwind, Apollo, GraphQL & MongoDB.
- · Link repo Link demo-video

CONTACT MANAGMENT

- · Full-stack application to efficiently manage imported contacts from various devices, enabling import, storage, editing, and deletion of Vcard files.
- · React Native, Node & PostgreSQL.
- · Link repo Link demo-video

PLAN MY PLATE

- · Meal planning app with integration of third-party APIs.
- · Built using React and Firebase, and deployed on Netlify.
- · Link repo Link demo-video Link real-demo

TALKER'S

- · A powerful CRUD web application with a database backend.
- · JavaScript, Express, Ejs, Postgresql & NPM dependencies.
- · Link repo Link demo-video

EXTRA EXPERIENCE

TEAM LEAD & HEAD COACH - Beat Community Fitness Cordoba, Argentina - Mar 2019 - Jun 2021

- Leading classes and providing high-quality coaching to members.
- Create and update workout programs that challenge members appropriately while ensuring scalability and inclusivity.
- Hiring, training, and evaluating coaches and other gym staff members fall under the Team Lead's purview.

PARALEGAL - Boetto Law Firm

Cordoba, Argentina - Jan 2014 - Jul 2018

- Conducting extensive research.
- Assisting in the preparation of legal documents, such as contracts, pleadings, motions, briefs, and other legal correspondence.
- Interacting with clients, and other involved parties to gather information, schedule meetings, and provide updates on case progress.

LANGUAGE



SPANISH - Native or bilingual proficiency



ENGLISH - Full professional proficiency



ITALIAN - Professional working proficiency